http://www.holliday-pigments.com/site-services/privacy-policy

News
Codes of conduct
Contact
.
About us
Venator at a glanceWhat we doOur valuesBoard of directorsVenator management team
Products and applications
Products
Titanium dioxideIron oxideUltramarinesBarium sulfateZinc sulfideInfrared reflecting pigmentsLithoponeChromium oxideCarbon blackComplex inorganic pigmentsPigment preparationsDriersWater treatment chemicalsFerrous sulfate heptahydrate
Applications
Active materialsAgricultureBatteriesCoatingsConstructionCosmetics and personal careFibersFilms (BoPET)FoodIndustrialInksPaperPharmaceuticalsPlasticsWater
Case Studies
Cosmetics innovationTransforming concrete Better plastic performance
Quality and Safety
Quality certificatesREACH
Investor relations
Financial newsCorporate governance
Governance overviewBoard of directorsManagement teamCommitteesGuidelines & ethics
Stock information
Stock quoteShare chartHistorical price lookupInvestment calculator
Events and presentations
Financial events
Financials
Annual Report & Proxy StatementSEC filings
Investor resources
Investor FAQInvestor contactsEmail alerts
Careers
Meet our peopleCurrent vacancies
News
Codes of conduct
Contact
.
About us
Venator at a glanceWhat we do
Our valuesBoard of directors
Venator management team
Products and applications
Products
Titanium dioxideIron oxideUltramarinesBarium sulfateZinc sulfideInfrared reflecting pigmentsLithoponeChromium oxideCarbon blackComplex inorganic pigmentsPigment preparationsDriersWater treatment chemicalsFerrous sulfate heptahydrate
Applications
Active materialsAgricultureBatteriesCoatingsConstructionCosmetics and personal careFibersFilms (BoPET)FoodIndustrialInksPaperPharmaceuticalsPlasticsWater
Case Studies
Cosmetics innovationTransforming concrete Better plastic performance
Quality and Safety
Quality certificatesREACH
Investor relations
Financial newsCorporate governance
Governance overviewBoard of directorsManagement teamCommitteesGuidelines & ethics
Stock information
Stock quoteShare chartHistorical price lookupInvestment calculator
Events and presentations
Financial events
Financials
Annual Report & Proxy StatementSEC filings
Investor resources
Investor FAQInvestor contactsEmail alerts
Careers
Meet our people
Current vacancies
HomeSite ServicesOnline Privacy Notice
Online Privacy Notice
Processing of Personal Data of Applicants
Privacy Shield Policy
We at Venator and our affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, “Venator”) respect your concerns about privacy. This Online Privacy Notice applies to personal information we collect on www.venatorcorp.com and www.venatorservice.com and any other Venator internet sites (collectively, the “Sites”), and describes how we use the information, with whom we share it and the choices available to users of our Sites regarding our use of the information. This notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how users can contact us about our privacy practices. This Online Privacy Notice applies to the majority of our websites; however, there may be occasions where there is a need to have a different privacy notice. As you visit other Venator websites, please check the Online Privacy Notice of each website that you visit as it may differ from this general Venator Online Privacy Notice.
Information We Collect
The types of personal information we collect through our Sites include:
Individual and business contact information (such as name, company name, job position, postal address, telephone numbers and email addresses)
Login credentials for the Sites
Contact information of others to whom users ask us to send information, as permitted by law
Cookie data and other browser-related information as further described in the “Information We Collect By Automated Means” section of this Online Privacy Notice, and
Other information that may be provided through the Sites (including through comments or questions fields)
Information you submit through our Careers pages is subject to a separate privacy notice available here
Information We Collect By Automated Means
When you visit our Sites, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, web server logs, web beacons and JavaScript.
Cookies
Cookies are files that websites send to your computer or another Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings on your device. Our Sites may use cookies such as HTTP cookies. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all the features of our Sites.
In conjunction with gathering information through cookies, our web servers may log information provided by your browser, such as your device type, browser type, domain, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. The web server logs also may record information such as the address of the web page that referred you to our Sites and the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. They also may log information about your interaction with the Sites, such as which pages you visit. We also may send instructions to your device using JavaScript or other computer languages to gather the sorts of information described above and other details about your interactions with the Sites.
Google Analytics
This Site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the Site analyze how users use it. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google Analytics Cookies may exist up to 2 years, if you do not delete them earlier.
IP-anonymisation is active on this Site. For visitors visiting the Site from within states that form part of the European Economic Area, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area before transfer to a Google server. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be first transferred to a Google server in the USA and truncated there.
Google will use this information on our behalf for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Site, compiling reports on website activity for us and providing to us other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP-address that your Browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this Site.
You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en (does not always work on mobile devices).
Google Analytics can also be deactivated on mobile and other devices by clicking the opt-out link here.
Social Plugins
Our Site uses social plugins (“Plugins”) provided by the social network LinkedIn (linkedin.com), which is operated by is LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Operator”). Its Plugins are identified by the LinkedIn or SlideShare logos of the “Share”-Button, as can be reviewed at http://linkedin.com. When you visit a page of our Site that contains a Plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the servers of the Operator. The Operator directly transfers the Plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the Site, enabling the Operator to receive information about your having accessed the respective page of our Site. This does also apply if you do not have a login or are not logged in at the network of the Operator. Your browser will transfer the information (including your IP address) to the servers of the respective Operator directly, where it will be stored and used by the Operator. The servers are based outside the European Economic Area.
We have no influence on the data gathered by the Plugins. For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by the respective Operators, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit LinkedIn's privacy policy: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy.
If you are a member of one of the above network and do not want the Operator to connect the data concerning your visit to our Site with your member data already stored by that Operator, please log out of the social network before entering our Site. In their privacy policies, the respective Operators may describe further options to block their Plugins. Also, at your option, you can use independent browser addons (e.g. „NoScript“ available at https://noscript.net) to keep all or some Plugins from loading.
E-Mail
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we receive a confirmation when you view our e-mail, if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to provide automatic feedback through e-mail, please adjust your e-mail preferences.
How We Use the Information We Collect
We may use the information described above to:
Provide our products and services
Establish and manage your Venator Service account or reset your password
Locate products and obtain safety data sheets, place orders, access invoices and other order-related documentation, obtain logistics information and facilitate warehousing requests
Respond to your inquiry or communicate with you about your requests, questions and comments
Send you an Investor Kit, financial information or other corporate information about Venator
Send information to your contacts if you ask us to do so
We may further use the information described above for our legitimate interests in marketing, service improvement and security to:
Communicate with you about, and administer your participation in, special events, conferences, programs, surveys and market research
Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; enhancing and improving our products and services; managing our communications; analyzing our products and services; and performing accounting, auditing, financial and economic analyses and other internal functions)
Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other liabilities, and
Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and the provisions of this Online Privacy Notice.
We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.
To the extent required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent before collecting information by automated means using cookies or similar automated means. Information about our cookie practices in the EU is available here.
Information We Share
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information we collect about you, except as described in this Online Privacy Notice. We may share personal information with service providers who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. We do not authorize these service providers to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. Examples of these service providers include entities that verify information and provide web hosting, analytics and marketing services. We also may share the personal information we obtain with our subsidiaries and affiliates.
In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by applicable law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government entities including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).
Your Choices
We offer you choices in connection with the personal information we collect from you. You may choose not to receive email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails. To update your preferences or submit a request, please contact us as indicated in the “How To Contact Us” section of this Online Privacy Notice. You may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us or object at any time on legitimate grounds to the processing of your personal information, and we will apply your preferences going forward. We will inform you on how to withdraw consent at the time we ask for your consent.
Data Transfers
We may transfer the personal information we collect about you through the Sites to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Online Privacy Notice.
Data transfers will be based on adequate standards such as data protection clauses approved by the European Commission or the Privacy Shield, as applicable. You may receive a copy of the clauses by contacting us as described below.
How We Protect Personal Information
We maintain administrative, organizational, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information obtained through the Sites against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.
Links To Other Websites and Apps
Our Sites may provide links to other websites or apps for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from us. Linked sites and apps may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review. To the extent any linked websites are not owned or controlled by us, we are not responsible for the websites’ or apps’ content, any use of the websites or apps, or the privacy practices of the websites or apps.
Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice
This Online Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post a prominent notice on our Sites to notify you of any significant changes to our Online Privacy Notice and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.
Identification of Data Controller
This Site is controlled by and operated on behalf of
Venator Materials PLC
Attention: Kevin Wilson, HR
Titanium House, Hanzard Drive
Wynyard Park, TS22 5FD UK
Phone: +44 1740 608001
privacy@venatorcorp.com
How To Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Online Privacy Notice, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by email at privacy@venatorcorp.com. You also may write to the above address.
Your Right to lodge a Complaint
If you are not satisfied with the way Venator handles your data or responds to your requests, you may contact the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) in the UK, which is the competent data protection authority for Venator. The contact details for the ICO can be found on their website. Alternatively, you may also contact the data protection authority in the country of your habitual residence.
Retention of Personal Information
Personal information collected through our Sites is retained only as long as (i) it is needed for the purposes for which it was obtained, in accordance with the provisions of this Online Privacy Notice or (ii) we have another lawful basis for retaining that data beyond the period for which it was necessary to serve the original purpose for collecting the data.
The above Venator Online Privacy Notice can be downloaded in PDF form here
HomeAbout usProducts and applicationsInvestor relationsCareers
Copyright © Venator Materials PLC.All rights reserved.
